莎伦！
Sharon!
她不在这儿
She's not here.
天啊 克里斯托弗 你看得到吗？
Oh, God. Christopher, can you see anything?
莎伦！
Sharon!
- 莎伦！- 她在那
- Sharon! - She's there.
莎伦！
Sharon!
宝贝！
Honey!
莎伦！
Sharon!
等等妈妈！
Wait for Mommy!
莎伦！
Sharon!
等等
Wait.
莎伦！宝贝！
Sharon! Honey!
我的天啊 莎伦！
Oh, my God. Sharon!
家
Home.
不！
No!
- 家！家！- 我们这就回家
- Home! Home! - We're going home.
寂静岭！
Silent Hill!
- 寂静岭！- 罗斯！
- Silent Hill! - Rose!
- 快醒醒 - 嘿
- Wake up. - Hey.
- 没事了 宝贝 有我们在 - 没事了
- It's okay, sweetie. We're here now. - It's okay. It's okay.
没事了
It's okay.
宝贝乖 我们这就回家
It's okay, baby. We're going right home.
- 我们该怎么办？- 会挺过去的
- What are we gonna do? - We'll get there.
总有办法 一定有办法的
We'll find a way through this. We'll find a way.
不
No.
- 她又说了那个地方 - 我知道
- She said it again. - I know.
- 没事了 宝贝 - 没事了 爸爸妈妈在这
- Come on, baby. It's okay. It's okay, baby. - It's okay. We're right here.
乖
It's okay.
没事了
没事了 宝贝
It's okay, baby.
《寂静岭》
- 想看吗？- 嗯
- Wanna see? - Sure.
在画什么呢 南瓜？
What are you doing there, pumpkin?
好一只大狮子呀 你自己画的？
This is an amazing lion. Did you do that all by yourself?
宝贝 你真棒
I'm so impressed with you, honey.
我们要做一次特别的旅行 你知道吧？
Hey, you know we're going on a special trip, don't you?
知不知道是要去哪儿？
Do you know where we're going?
不知道？
No?
亲爱的 有时候你睡觉的时候 会四处走动
Honey, sometimes when you go to sleep, you go on a little walk.
有时候 还会提到一个地方
And sometimes you talk about a place…
叫做寂静岭
… called Silent Hill.
我不记得了
I don't remember.
没关系 宝贝
Oh, that's okay, sweetie.
所以我们要去那里 好让你记起来
That's why we're gonna go there, so you can remember.
爸爸不去吗？
Daddy's not coming?
不 宝贝 就我们俩
No, sweetie. It's gonna be just you and me.
休息结束了 宝贝
Break's over, sweetie.
睡醒了？
You awake?
可以走了么？
You wanna go?
（岂不知我们要审判天使吗 岂不知圣徒要审判世界吗）
（《新约·哥林多前书》 教会宣）
该死 罗斯 怎么回事？
Damn it, Rose. What's going on?
我是罗斯·达·西尔瓦
Hi, this is Rose Da Silva.
请留言 我稍候会回复
Please leave a message, and I'll call you back.
（美国鬼城网）
（西弗吉尼亚 寂静岭）
不 罗斯
Oh, no, Rose.
（寂静岭 「不洁之镇」 地下火燃烧至今）
亲爱的 你醒啦？
Honey, you're awake?
走了好远哦
Long drive.
能问你个事儿 宝贝？
Can I ask you something, sweetie?
为什么要换你画的画？
Why did you change your pictures?
我没有
I didn't.
- 妈咪？- 不记得了？
- Mommy? - You can't remember?
我不喜欢这个 妈咪
No. I don't like that, Mommy.
- 宝贝 你不记得了？- 谁做的？
- Baby, you can't remember doing this? - Who did that?
- 好了 没事了 - 妈咪 是谁做的？
- Hey, hey, baby, it's okay. - Mommy, who did that?
乖 没事了 妈妈在这
It's okay, honey. Mommy's here.
在车里等我一下好吗？
Can you wait in the car for me?
可以坐前面吗？
Can I sit in front?
- 当然可以啦 - 好吧
- Of course you can sit in the front. - Okay.
吉米 一份火腿加起司白面包
Jimmy, we need a ham and cheese on white.
嗨
Hi.
我来付油钱
I just wanna pay for the gas.
请问到寂静岭该走哪条路？
And can you tell me the best way to get to Silent Hill?
我在地图上找不到
I can't seem to find it on the map.
- 为什么要去那？- 我 我看过一些报道
- Why do you wanna go there? - I… I read about it.
路走不通了
Road don't go through no more.
你的卡被冻结了
Your card was declined.
小家伙
Hey there.
- 你没事吧？- 不要和陌生人说话
- Is everything all right? - Don't talk to strangers.
乖孩子
Good girl.
好的 多谢帮忙
All right. Well, thanks for your help.
为什么要冻结我的卡？
Why did you cut off the cards?
别想靠这个阻止我
That's not gonna stop me from taking her there.
亲爱的 听我说 我们得送莎伦去医院
Listen, honey, we gotta put Sharon in a hospital.
她需要专人守护 接受药物治疗
She needs constant care, and she needs medication.
吃药没用
The medication doesn't work.
已经越来越严重了
She's getting worse every day.
亲爱的 领养处的人说 她来自西弗吉尼亚
Honey, the adoption people said Sharon came from West Virginia…
寂静岭也在西弗吉尼亚
… and Silent Hill is in West Virginia.
我不会放弃她 克里斯 决不
I'm not giving up on her, Chris. I'm not.
你到底看过那些网页没有？
Have you actually read the websites, Rose?
看过了 克里斯
Yes, Chris, I read them.
就相信我一次 求你了
Just trust me on this, please. Just trust me on this.
亲爱的 听我说
Listen, honey…
- 我爱莎伦就像 - 我得走了 克里斯
- I love Sharon every bit as much as I… - Chris, I gotta go.
就像爱你一样
… I love you.
- 需要帮忙吗 女士？- 没事我们很好 谢谢
- Need any help, ma'am? - No, we're… We're fine, thanks.
我们没事
We're fine.
到了？
Are we there?
还没有 亲爱的
Not yet, honey.
系好安全带
Keep your seatbelt fastened.
嗨！
Hey!
妈咪！
Mommy!
没事 只是收音机
It's okay. It's just the radio.
- 我这就关 - 妈咪！
- I'm turning it off. - Mommy!
莎伦？
Sharon?
莎伦！
Sharon!
来人啊！救命啊！
Somebody! Help!
救命！
Please!
这儿出了车祸！
We've had an accident!
来人啊！
Anybody!
莎伦 宝贝
Sharon. Honey.
灰烬
Ashes.
（寂静岭欢迎您）
莎伦！
Sharon!
等等！
Wait!
莎伦！
Sharon!
等等！
Wait!
莎伦！
Sharon!
莎伦？
Sharon?
宝贝？
Honey?
怎么回事？
What's happening?
妈咪
Mommy.
莎伦
Sharon.
莎伦？
Sharon?
有人吗？
Hello?
等等！
Wait!
莎伦
Sharon.
救命！
Help me!
Help!
救命！
Help me! Help!
谁来救救我！妈的！
Someone! Shit!
滚开！滚开！
Get off me! Get off!
Get off! Get off!
滚开！
Get off me!
不！滚开！
No! Get off me!
不！滚开！滚开！
No! Get off me! Get off me!
滚开！
Get off!
寂静岭的入口 为黑暗力量所掌控
Only the dark one opens and closes the door to Silent Hill.
麻烦你
Please.
我不知道这儿是怎么回事 你知道吗？
I don't know what's happening. Do you know what's going on here?
我女儿
My daughter.
我在找我女儿 真担心她出事
I'm looking for my daughter. I'm afraid that she's been hurt.
我们都失去了孩子
We've all lost our children.
生命从此黯淡无光
Our light.
他们欺骗了我
They deceived me.
心中的罪恶
Their evil.
还有仇恨
Their hate.
令他们伤害了我的孩子
They hurt my child.
虐待她
They did terrible things to her.
阿蕾莎
Alessa.
这是我女儿 莎伦
This is my daughter, Sharon.
她有梦游症 请你小心
She sleepwalks, so you have to be careful…
要是看到她 请让她等着我
… but if you see her, please, tell her to wait for me.
哦 她是我女儿
Yes, she's mine.
- 这是我的 - 是我的
- It was mine. - It's mine.
- 我的 - 我的！
- It's mine. - It's mine!
- 是我的！- 放手！
- It's mine! - Get off me!
在烈火中 她咽下他们的仇恨
Into the fire she swallowed their hate.
- 嘿 - 嗯
- Hi there. - Yeah.
我妻子 昨夜经过这里
Listen, my wife, she came through here last night.
- 看见过吗？- 我女儿上夜班
- Maybe you saw her? - Daughter worked night shift.
事实上 她是要去寂静岭
Actually, she was heading for this place, Silent Hill.
- 怎么走？- 没路可走
- How do I get there? - You don't.
因为煤矿起火 小镇被关闭了
Town's closed down because of the coal fire…
地下仍有余火燃烧
… still burning underground, you know?
呼吸几口那儿的煤烟 能要你的命
Breathe enough of them fumes, oh, bound to kill you.
告诉我
Okay…
是哪条岔路？
… where's the turnoff?
莎伦？
Sharon?
快点
Come on.
我是克里斯 请留言
Hi, this is Chris. Please leave a message.
克里斯托弗 是我
Christopher, it's me.
我在寂静岭 抱歉我太莽撞了
I'm in Silent Hill. I'm sorry, I made a mistake.
莎伦不见了 我想我知道她在哪
Sharon's lost, but I think I know where she is…
我现在就去学校找她
… so I'm going to the school to look for her.
我这边不对劲 好吗？需要你的帮助
I'm not okay, all right? I need your help.
求求你 快来吧
Please, please, hurry.
操 快点！
Fuck. Come on!
女士 请把手放在方向盘上
Ma'am, I want you to put both hands on the wheel.
两手放在方向盘上
Put both hands on the wheel.
女士 小女孩哪去了？
Where's the little girl, ma'am?
求求你 我女儿不见了 需要你的帮助
Please, my daughter, she's gone. I need your help.
- 下车 - 什么？
- Get out of the car. - What?
快点
Move it.
老天 你要干嘛？
Jesus, what are you doing?
- 你被捕了 - 什么？
- You're under arrest. - What?
你所说的一切都将作为呈堂证供
Anything you say can and will be used against you in a court of law.
你没弄明白 这个地方不对劲
I don't think you understand. There's something weird going on.
我的女儿莎伦现在十分危险
My daughter, Sharon, she's in danger.
你要是真关心她 就不会踩油门逃跑了
If you really cared, you wouldn't have sped off.
听我说 她病了 是梦游症
Listen to me, she 's ill. She sleepwalks.
冷静点 我会找到那小女孩
Just calm right down. I'm gonna find the little girl.
伯纳特警官呼叫总部 完毕
Officer Bennett to base, over.
总部请回话 完毕！
Base, do you copy, over!
- 该死 - 你在流血
- Shit. - You're bleeding.
我翻车的时候
Cracked my head on the road pretty good when my bike went down.
头给撞了个正着 看来是晕过去了一会
I must have been out for a while.
- 能走么？- 嗯
- You all right to walk? - Sure.
看来我们得步行回Brahams了
Then it looks like we'll be hiking back to Brahams.
什么？
What?
我要带你回警局
You're going back to the station.
- 你在开玩笑吧？- 没有
- Are you kidding? - Nope.
你可听到我说的话？
Have you heard a single word I've said?
- 听到了 - 你可听进去
- Yeah, I hear you. - Have you heard…
哪怕是一个字？
… a single word I've said?
我确定她就在学校 我们得回去
I'm sure she's at the school, we just need to turn around…
寂静岭 对不起
… Silent Hill… sorry…
莎伦 不见
… Sharon… lost…
我想 我去学校找她
… think I know where… going to the school to look for her…
这里不对劲
I'm not okay…
我需要你 你的帮助 求求你 快来
I need your… Your help. Please, hurry!
对不起先生 此路不通 请回吧
Sorry, sir, this road is closed. You'll have to turn around.
我在找我妻子 她可能是走的这条路
I'm looking for my wife. She may have come through here.
她开一辆银色「吉普-自由者」 俄亥俄牌照
She drives a Jeep Liberty. Silver, Ohio plates.
长官 那辆吉普 是这位先生的妻子在开
Sir, this man's wife was driving the Jeep.
带过来
Bring him down.
- 过来 - 你见过她？
- Come on. - You've seen her?
她在哪？
Where is she?
探长托马斯·古奇 天气不错啊 你说呢？
Inspector Thomas Gucci. Enjoying the weather, are you?
看在上帝的份上 我在找我妻子
For God's sake, I'm trying to find my wife.
我知道 稍等
I know. Hang on a second.
你说的那辆车 我们找到了
Now, that vehicle you were talking about, we found it.
在这座桥的尽头 里面没人
It's at the end of the bridge here, but it's empty.
没有任何迹象表明有人受伤
We've got no indication anyone's come under any harm.
- 老天 - 你不介意的话
- Good Christ. - Now, you mind telling me…
能告诉我你妻子来这做什么吗 你是？
… what your wife's doing up here, Mr?
- 达·西尔瓦 克里斯·达·西尔瓦 - 很荣幸见到你 克里斯
- Da Silva, Chris Da Silva. - My pleasure, Chris…
我们马上行动 就能尽快找到她
The faster we start looking, the faster we're gonna find her.
好了 暂且打住
All right, hold your horses, hold your horses, Chris.
我也失踪了一名手下
I've also got a missing deputy.
以我对警官西比尔·伯纳特的了解
And knowing Officer Cybil Bennett the way I do…
她应该正在寻找你的妻女
… she's probably out there looking for your wife and daughter.
鲍比 不要让任何人通过路障
Bobby, make sure no one comes through that barricade.
我们这就去寂静岭
We're gonna get our asses up to Silent Hill.
- 到里面转转 - 是 长官
- Let's take a look around. - Yes, sir.
让克里斯告诉我到底是怎么回事
While Chris here tells me what's going on.
她是昨天起失踪的 在博拉姆斯停车加油的时候
She disappeared yesterday. I spoke to her…
她还和我通过电话
… when she stopped for gas in Brahams.
为什么半夜还要到这里来？
Why were you coming up here in the middle of the night?
- 我想帮她 - 你们这些城里人
- I thought it would help her. - You people. You get off the highway…
带着一堆麻烦事 就往乡下钻
… from whatever big city, bringing all your sick problems with you.
你怎么就不听我说呢？
Why aren't you listening to me?
两年前 一个家伙来到这里
We had a guy come up here two years ago…
将途中拐走的男孩 扔进了一个矿井的通风口
… snatched a little boy from a rest stop, dropped him into a mine vent.
我决不允许这样的事情再次发生
I never wanna see anything like that again.
我不知道你是怎么想的 但你是在帮倒忙
Look, I don't know what you're thinking, but you're not helping.
我决不会伤害自己的女儿
There is no way I would ever harm my own daughter.
我怎么知道她是你女儿？
How do I even know she is your daughter?
来吧
Come on.
怎么回事？
What the hell?
好了
Okay.
现在你明白我的意思了吧？
Now do you see what I'm talking about?
能不能把这手铐打开？
Will you take these handcuffs off me?
不行 继续走
No. Get walking.
托卢卡湖那头有一个火警瞭望塔
There's a fire-lookout tower on the far side of Toluca Lake.
- 那里应该有无线电 - 臭屁警察
- It should have a radio. - Fuck you, you stupid cop.
这里完全与世隔绝
This place is completely cut off.
你根本不知道出了什么问题
You have no idea what's going on. Hey!
嗨 上面这位！
Hey, you up there!
我是警察！
I'm a police officer!
怎么回事？
What's going on?
那是什么？
What is that?
退后
Stand back.
老天 快打他
Jesus Christ, shoot it.
不许动！
Stay where you are!
站住！
Stop!
MIDWICH小学
Midwich Elementary School
莎伦！
Sharon!
（恨恶义人的 必被定罪）
（教务室）
罗斯
Rose.
国
COUNTRY
家
HOME
忠
LOYALTY
神
GOD
达·西尔瓦夫人 我是警察
Mrs. Da Silva, I am an officer of the law…
我会带你到安全地方
… and I will take you to safety.
达·西尔瓦夫人 我是警察
Mrs. Da Silva, I am an officer of the law…
我会带你到安全地方
… and I will take you to safety.
- 怎么不让我来喊？- 像这种
- Why don't you let me do that? - Ninety percent of the time…
妻子带着女儿私奔
… when a wife takes a run…
逃到这种地方来
… she takes the daughter to a place like this…
八成是和她丈夫斗气
… I'd say she's damn mad at her husband.
你很喜欢挖别人家底是吧？
You like hauling skeletons out of your family closet?
不总是 不过现在 倒是可以挖挖我们车底
No, not all the time, but we're driving on top of them right now.
地下的煤矿还在燃烧
Coal fire's still burning underneath.
看到那边的理发店了？
You see the barbershop over there?
- 曾经是我父亲的 - 你父亲？
- Used to be my father's. - Your father?
他死了
He's dead.
74年11月的那场大火
November '74, when the fire caught.
虽然人们尽了全力疏散
They tried to evacuate this place as quick as they could…
但在那地狱般的大火里 死的死 失踪的失踪
… but it was hellish, people were dying and disappearing.
甚至有一半的尸体都找不到
Hell, they couldn't even find half the bodies.
寂静岭的末日
That was the end of Silent Hill.
都是好人 大部分是
These were good people, most of them.
其他的 多多少少吧
Some, you might say deserved it.
算是罪有应得
A little bit.
莎伦！
Sharon!
莎伦
Sharon.
（巫女）
你藏在哪？
Where are you hiding?
烧死巫女！烧死巫女！烧死巫女！
Burn the witch! Burn the witch! Burn the witch!
阿蕾莎·格雷斯彼
Alessa Gillespie.
等等！
Wait!
没事了
It's okay.
没事
It's gonna be okay.
我一定会帮你的
I promise I'm gonna help you.
柯林
COLIN
（- 你敢吗 - 那你呢 - 你敢我就敢）
快点
Come on.
噢 天啊
Oh, God.
快
Come on.
神啊 救救我 求你救我
Help me. Oh, God. Please, please, help me. Help…
救救我 救救我
Help me. Please, help me. Help me. Help me, please.
又来了
It's happening again.
救命！
Help me! Please! Please!
快点！快点！
Come on! Come on!
罗斯！
Rose!
莎伦！
Sharon!
罗斯！
Rose!
罗斯
Rose.
- 罗斯！- 戴上口罩
- Rose! - Put your mask on.
罗斯 你在哪？
Rose, where are you?
- 我能感觉到她 - 你什么？
- I felt her. - You what?
她的香水
Her perfume.
- 她来过这里 - 谁？
- She was here. - Who was?
- 我妻子 - 她没来过这儿 戴上口罩
- My wife. - She wasn't here. Put this mask on.
- 香水味 - 戴上口罩呼吸
- Perfume. - Breathe. Through that mask.
得了 我们走 走这边
Come on, let's go. We're gonna go this way.
克里斯
Chris, come on.
- 她来过过这里 - 不 她没有
- She was here. - No, no, she wasn't here.
我有感应
I know it.
行了
Come on.
我们继续找吧
Come on. Let's keep looking.
滚开！滚开！滚开！
Get off! Get off! Get off!
把那根铁管拿过来
Get me that pipe.
罗斯 铁管！
Rose, the pipe!
好的 好的
Okay. Okay.
- 拿到了 - 快点
- I got it. I got it. - Quick, come on!
能逃出去吗？
Can we get out of here?
我们被困住了
We're trapped.
最后一匣
Last mag.
- 就剩这么点子弹了？- 嗯
- That's all the bullets you got? - Yeah.
谢谢
Thanks.
你听见了？
You hear that?
就是他
That's him.
蹲下！快蹲下！
Stay down! Stay down!
老天！
Jesus Christ!
蹲下！
Get down!
该死！
Shit!
怎么了？
What?
他妈的怎么回事？
What the fuck?
你也看到了？那是真的？
You saw that, right? That was real?
这他妈是怎么回事？
What the fuck is going on?
这的确很疯狂 我知道
All right, I know this is crazy. I know.
我们要冷静 我孩子不在这里
We gotta calm right down, because my kid is not here…
在这「状况」再次发生前 得找到我女儿
… and I've gotta find her before this happens again.
我都不知道从何找起
I don't even know where to start.
我找到这个
I found this.
是一个饭店的
It's from a hotel.
我不知道在哪 但她就在里面
I don't know where it is, but she is in this hotel.
饭店？
Hotel?
不会有事了
It's gonna be okay.
我们不会有事的
We're gonna be okay.
好了 放弃尝试吧 好吗？
Now, don't be trying anything, all right?
我们留人整夜驻守这里
We got men up here all night long.
会找到你的妻女的
We're gonna find your wife, we're gonna find your daughter.
不能让老百姓到处乱走
Can't have civilians wandering around on their own.
你隐瞒了什么
You're not telling me everything.
这里到底发生过什么？
What really happened up here?
往事就让它入土为安吧
Just let it rest in peace.
- 查询台 - 请找下托卢卡郡的档案
- Directory assistance. - Toluca County Archives, please.
请稍等
One moment.
- 关于什么的？- 听着
- Archives? - Yeah, listen.
你有没有关于寂静岭的记录？
Do you have the records there from Silent Hill?
- 什么记录？- 警方记录
- Which records, sir? - The police records.
抱歉 那些记录是绝密档
Sorry, sir, those records are confidential.
不 不 我不能… 不 听着 我
No, no, I can't… No, listen, I…
抱歉 我没法提供相关信息
Sorry, sir, I can't access that information.
- 听着 该死的 - 先生
- Listen, goddamn it. - Sir.
- 我有急事 - 我不能
- This is an emergency. - I can't…
我没法帮你
I can't help you.
他们说这儿闹鬼
They used to say this place was haunted.
我想没错
I think they were right.
（大饭店）
救命！不！
Help! No!
- 滚开 - 快
- Stay away. - Come on.
滚开 罪人！
Stay away, sinner!
退后！
Get back!
在这里
It's here.
信仰是我们的掘墓人 带来灭顶之灾
Faith is our destroyer. Faith has brought us doom.
- 滚！- 嘿 嘿
- Get back! - Hey, hey!
- 滚！- 住手！
- Get back! - Hey, stop!
你 这扔第一块石头的人
Think you of thee who cast the first stone.
没有牧羊人的羊羔 没有羊群的牧羊人
Lambs without a shepherd, shepherd without a flock.
你的罪恶将你困诸此地
It's your sins which hold you here.
- 少造谣了！- 冷静！
- Stop your lies! - Calm down!
冷静点 没事了
Calm down, it's okay.
- 我们不会伤害你 - 她走了
- We're not gonna hurt you. - She's gone.
你叫什么名字？
What's your name?
安娜 我叫安娜
Anna. My name is Anna.
安娜 这儿到底是怎么回事？她是谁？
What's going on here, Anna? Who was that?
- 我见过她 - 达利亚是被赶出来的
- I've seen her before. - Dahlia was cast out.
连黑暗力量也不要她
Not even the darkness wants her.
- 她也失去了女儿 - 什么？
- She's lost her daughter too. - What?
- 罪人应该断子绝孙 - 你在这里做什么 安娜？
- Sinners deserve to lose their spawn. - What are you doing here, Anna?
母亲需要更多食物
Mother needs more food.
你是说 还有其他人？
You mean there are other people here?
克里斯贝拉保护我们
Christabella keeps us safe.
- 安娜 - 我们在教堂避难
- Anna. - We take refuge in the church.
安娜 听我说
Anna, listen to me.
我女儿不见了 她一个人
I've lost my daughter. She's all alone.
能想象她有多害怕吗？
Can you imagine how frightened she must feel?
告诉我 有没有见过她
Tell me, have you seen her?
知不知道她在哪？
Do you know where she is?
她要是有信仰 就能活下来
If she has faith, she might survive.
要是没有
If not…
这个我拿着
I'm taking this.
见过这个么？
Have you seen this?
我在学校见过
I've seen it at the school.
所有的建筑上都有 老祖先修的
It's on all the buildings the elders of my elders built.
是我们团结和信仰的标志
It's a symbol of our unity, a symbol of our faith.
罗斯 看这个
Rose, look at this.
- 是什么？- 和你的一样
- What is it? - Just like yours.
- 在哪找到的？- 地上到处都是
- Where did you find it? - They're all over the floor.
罗斯
Rose.
来看
Check this out.
- 在几号拿的？- 111号
- What number did you take this from? - 111.
我们去111号房
We gotta go to room 111.
寂静岭警方记录
Silent Hill Police Records
古奇
Gucci.
三度烧伤
Third Degree Burns
受害者照片
Photograph of Victim
- 查寻台 - 你好
- Directory assistance. - Yeah.
我要查询托卢卡郡立孤儿院
Toluca County Orphanage, please.
请稍后
One moment, please.
- 嗯 我找到了相关信息 - 好
- Yes, I have that information for you. - Yeah.
能告诉我地址吗？
Can you give me that address?
我们离避难所太远了
We are wandering far from refuge here.
没得选择了 带上她吧
Let's keep her with us. She's all we got.
没有111号房
There's no room 111.
第一场火
The first burning.
- 是什么 安娜？- 第一场火
- What is it, Anna? - The first burning.
那时这小镇还没有名字
Before the town had a name.
祖先们为了保持纯净
The elders of my elders kept us pure.
小镇的祖先原来是巫女猎人
The founders of this town were witch-hunters.
靠烧死巫女来驱退黑暗
Burning the witch held back the darkness.
好阻止世界末日「天启」的到来
It stopped the apocalypse.
就是这儿
It's here.
这里有个房间
There's a room in here.
看这里
Look at this.
来
Here.
该死
Damn.
这是什么地方？
What is this place?
不知道 到了另外一栋房子了
I don't know. We're in the next building.
是什么工厂吧
Some factory, maybe?
看来这里曾起过火
Looks like there was a fire.
罗斯！
Rose!
你是谁？
Who are you?
没事了
It's okay.
别怕 我保证不会伤害你
Don't be scared. I promise I'm not gonna hurt you.
罗斯？
Rose?
加油
Okay. Come on.
Come on.
没事了
It's okay. Hey.
没事
It's okay.
没事了
我不会伤害你
I'm not gonna hurt you.
我的天
Oh, my God.
你简直就是她的双胞胎妹妹
You could be her twin.
你是阿蕾莎？
Are you Alessa?
我的莎伦在哪？
Where's my Sharon?
看着我
Look at me.
我在燃烧
I'm burning.
罗斯？
Rose?
罗斯 老天
Rose? My God.
- 你怎么过去的？- 她到哪去了？
- How did you get over there? - Where is she?
抓住这个
Grab onto it.
- 荡回来 - 好
- Now swing back around. - Okay.
- 你没事吧？- 嗯
- Are you all right? - Yeah.
你在那边做什么？
What the hell were you doing over there?
这样会没命的
You're gonna get yourself killed.
我刚见到了达利亚的女儿
I think I just saw Dahlia's daughter.
是她带我们到这里来
She was the one that brought us here.
你在说什么？
What are you talking about?
是她害我撞了车
She was the one that made me crash my car.
阿蕾莎
Alessa.
我们从不提这个名字
We don't say her name.
安娜 这就是那个封印？
That's the seal, isn't it, Anna?
你们信仰的标志？
The symbol of your faith?
这里一定发生过很可怕的事情
Something terrible happened here.
得走了 我们得走了！
We have to leave. We have to leave!
- 黑暗就要来了 - 快走
- The darkness is coming! - Let's go.
快点！
Let's go!
教堂并不远
The church isn't far.
- 跑 快跑！- 罗斯 快点！
- Run. Run! - Rose, come on!
罗斯！
Rose!
快！
Hurry!
罗斯
Rose.
- 快来！- 我们走
- Come! - We gotta go.
- 罗斯 快 - 我见过这个
- Rose, come on. - I've seen this.
罗斯 我们走！
Rose, let's go!
- 西比尔！- 罗斯 快
- Cybil! - Rose, come on.
西比尔！
Cybil!
你们不是躲避灾难 只是逃避内心的恐惧
You run not towards sanctuary but from your fears.
不要同流合污 他们是骗子 受诅咒的人
Do not join the others. They are deceivers. They are damned.
- 我们得进去 - 不！
- We gotta get inside. - No!
他们是披着羊皮的狼
They are wolves in the skin of sheep.
自取灭亡 还要拖你陪葬
They brought about their own hell. They'll take you with them.
- 胡说八道！- 嘿！
- Filth and lies! - Hey!
住手！
Stop it!
求求你 我见过你女儿阿蕾莎
Please. I've seen your daughter. I've seen Alessa.
- 要来了！- 她死了是不是？
- It's coming! - She's dead, isn't she?
烈火无法清洁 只会越烧越黑
Fire doesn't cleanse, it blackens.
- 听我说 - 罗斯 快！
- Listen to me. - Rose, hurry!
她和莎伦长得一模一样
She looks exactly like Sharon.
她带我们来这儿的 对不对？
She brought us here, didn't she?
为什么？她到底要做什么？
Why? What does she want?
恶魔会随着仇恨一同苏醒
Evil wakes in vengeance.
要小心做出选择
Be careful what you choose.
罗斯！
Rose!
天啊
Oh, God, no.
- 巫女！- 她是恶魔！
- Witches! - She's evil.
别让巫女靠近！
Keep away the witches!
- 不 - 赶她们出去！
- No. - Send them back!
不是
No.
我们迷路了
We're lost.
这里是神圣的避难所
This is a sanctuary.
克里斯贝拉 她们引诱了我的安娜
Please, Christabella, they lured my Anna.
将她送到恶魔手里
They gave her to the fiend.
埃莉诺 你一定记得 安娜没有依教规行事
Eleanor, you must remember that Anna went against our laws.
她独自外出 闯入恶魔的领地
She went alone outside into the devil's playground.
她不关这两个陌生人的事
She was not the responsibility of these two strangers.
等会儿再来对付她们
We'll deal with them later.
现在我们要祈祷
Now we must pray.
我看见他们
And then I saw them…
从他们面前天地都逃避
… from whose presence earth and heaven fled away.
再无家可回
And no home was left to them.
我看见他们
And then I saw them…
从他们面前天地都逃避
… from whose presence earth and heaven fled away.
再无家可回
And no home was left to them.
我又看见死了的人 无论大小
And I saw the dead, the great and the small…
照他们所行的受审判
… and they were judged according to their deeds.
我又看见死了的人 无论大小
And I saw the dead, the great and the small…
照他们所行的受审判
… and they were judged according to their deeds.
若有人名字没记在生命册上
And anyone's name not found written in the book of life…
他们就被扔在火湖里
… they will be thrown into the lake of fire.
托卢卡郡立孤儿院
Toluca County Orphanage
现在我躺下睡觉
And now I lay me down to sleep…
请主守护我的灵魂
… I pray the Lord my soul to keep.
如果我醒来之前死去
If I should die before I wake…
请主带我灵魂同行
… I pray the Lord my soul to take.
阿门
Amen.
好了 孩子们 快上床睡觉吧
All right, girls, into bed. Quickly, now.
下雨天 也无处可去啦
No better place to be on a rainy night.
琳茜 快点 那位 拿好你的小熊 真乖
In you go, Lindsey, thattagirl. You've got your bear, that's a girl.
熄灯后不许讲话
No. No talking after lights are out.
晚安 孩子们
Good night, children.
上帝保佑你们
And God bless.
抱歉 玛格丽特修女 真的等不得
I'm sorry, Sister Margaret, this really can't wait.
我不知什么这么急
I can't imagine why.
9年前
Nine years ago…
这所孤儿院外发现了一个女婴
… a baby was left outside this orphanage.
我和妻子领养了她
My wife and I were the ones who adopted her.
我为你感到高兴 达·西尔瓦先生
I'm very happy for you, Mr. Da Silva…
但我不能交出这里孩子的资料
… but I can't give out information on our children.
听我说
Look.
有个女孩 和我女儿一模一样
That girl, she looks exactly like my daughter.
我帮不了你 抱歉
I can't help you, I'm sorry.
- 很晚了 - 她该有40岁了
- It's late. - She must be 40 now.
我到哪能找到她？
Where can I find her?
这不是她一个人的故事
This story isn't hers alone…
- 而是关系到所有人！- 你这种人
- … but all of ours! - You people.
你是自找麻烦
You got yourself something.
知道什么麻烦么 克里斯？非法闯入？
You know what you got now, Chris? How about breaking and entering?
照这个样子 还得加上伤害罪
By the looks of this, a little assault as well.
谢谢你 托马斯
Thank you, Thomas.
- 不能再追究下去了 - 不会的 修女
- This can't go any farther. - It won't, Sister.
我认识一些12岁的小毛孩
You know, I have some 12-year-olds…
都比你会掩饰行踪
… who cover their tracks better than you do.
这是什么？
What's this?
古奇 认得她么？
Look, Gucci, do you know her?
她就是我女儿的亲生母亲？
Is that my daughter's birth mother?
- 转过身去 - 你要做什么？
- Look, turn around. - What are you doing?
是的 我认识那女孩
I knew that girl. I did.
我听说她没能熬过那晚
I was told she didn't make it through the night.
起火的那晚
The night of the fire.
寂静岭烧起大火那一晚
The night of the big fire in Silent Hill.
那些人
There were these people…
狂热的教徒
… these fanatics.
残忍地虐待了那个女孩
What they did to that child was terrible.
那是30年前的事了 早已过去
That was 30 years ago, and it's over now.
据我所知 并没有过去
Not as far as I'm concerned.
那又怎么样 城里人？
What's it gonna be, city boy?
我可以送你进监狱
I can put you in jail…
或者你可以回家
… or you can go home.
这就是你所谓的正义？
And that's your definition of justice?
正义的形式有很多种 克里斯
Many different forms of justice, Chris.
人类的 上帝的
See, you've got man's, God's…
甚至恶魔的
… and even the devil's.
到底哪一种 不由你说了算
Certain forms you just can't control.
我要你马上回家
So I want you to go home now…
躺倒温暖的床上
… to your nice warm bed…
让我来对付这个小镇
… and let me deal with this town…
和过去30年里的变故.
… and what has happened over the last 30 years.
好了？故事结束
Okay? End of story.
（全能的主啊 在他手里…）
先告诉我你们怎么来到这里
Tell me first how you got here.
老实说 我不知道怎么到这里的
Honestly, I don't know how I got here.
现在 我丢了小女儿
Right now, I've lost my little girl…
而且我明白必须要到这教堂来
… and all I know is that I'm supposed to be in this church.
你有信仰么？
Are you a person of faith?
- 我爱我女儿 - 没问你这个
- I love my daughter. - That's not what I asked.
凭什么由你来决断？
Who are you to judge?
就凭昔日的灵魂还未安息
We judge because the souls of history hang in the balance.
而信仰从未让我们失望
Because our faith has never failed us.
是信仰让地狱的黑暗无法蔓延
Our faith keeps the darkness of hell at bay.
那就用你们的信仰 帮我找到女儿
Then use your faith to help me find my little girl.
只有恶魔知道她在哪
Only the demon knows where she is.
那告诉我 到哪去找这个恶魔？
Then tell me, where do I find this demon?
没人能从黑暗力量中心
No one has ever returned from the core of the darkness…
恶魔藏身之处逃脱
… where the demon lies in wait.
她不会帮忙的 我们走
She's not gonna help us. Let's go.
你要是愿意面对恶魔 找到女儿
If you wish to face the demon to find your daughter…
我不阻止你
… I won't stop you.
- 克里斯贝拉 不能去那下面 - 闭嘴 亚当
- Christabella, they can't go down… - Silence, Adam.
也许你的信仰能保佑你
Perhaps your faith will protect you.
也许不能
Perhaps not.
要是你不想去
If you don't wanna do this…
我理解
… I'll understand.
莎伦是领养的
Sharon's adopted…
可我是她母亲
… but I'm her mother.
从见到她的第一眼起 我就这样认定
I knew that from the moment I first laid eyes on her.
她真幸运 有你这样的母亲
She's lucky to have you.
在孩子眼里 母亲就是上帝
Mother is God in the eyes of a child.
安静
Quiet.
我们现在在他的领地了
We're in his domain now.
看这个地图 记下来
Look at this map. Memorize it.
你的记忆能救你的命
Your memory may save your life.
- 看到这个房间了？- 是的
- Do you see this room? - Yeah.
恶魔就在这
That is where the darkness lies.
恶魔在这栋楼的中心
The demon is in the bowels of this building.
藏在一张天真无邪的面孔下面
It hides behind the face of an innocent.
你是说孩子？
You mean a child?
不要相信你的眼睛 它们在欺骗你
Don't believe your eyes. Your eyes will lie to you.
信仰才是唯一的真理
Faith is the only truth.
我会为你祈祷 罗斯
I will pray for you, Rose…
不过并不期待你和伙伴 能活着出来
… but I won't expect you and your friend to return.
再见
Goodbye.
亚当
Adam.
左 右
Left. Right.
左 左
Left. Left.
- 右 右 左 - 带他们到下一层
- Right. Right. Left. - Take them to the lower level.
- 底层？- 照着做 然后回来
- In the basement? - Do it, then return.
- 左 3A - 但是
- Left. 3A. - But…
- 右 4A - 我说了 照做
- Right. 4A. - I said, do it.
- 左 左 右 - 罗斯罗斯
- Left. Left. Right. - Rose. Rose.
- 左 右 左 左 - 罗斯 她要害死你
- Left. Right. Left. Left. - Rose, she's killing you.
- 罗斯！- 让我去
- Rose! - Let me do this.
我必须去
I need to do this.
拿着
Take this.
光会吸引他们 但没有光你什么也看不见
They'll be drawn to the light, but you won't be able to see without it.
谢谢
Thank you.
- 这样真的可以？- 可以
- So this thing actually works? - It will.
如果恶魔需要你的话
If the demon wants you, it will.
请饶恕我
Forgive me.
看来我们终日拾荒已成习惯 我想这是你的
We've lived too long as scavengers. I believe this is yours.
巫女！她女儿和阿蕾莎一模一样
Witch! Her child's the likeness of Alessa.
她女儿就是孽种
Her child's the next vessel.
阻止她！不要让巫女下去
Stop her! Don't let the witches go down!
快点！
Come on!
离她远点！
Get off her!
找到她
Find her.
不！等等！西比尔！
No! Wait! Cybil!
西比尔！开门！
Cybil! Open the door!
不！
No!
8A
8A.
7A 右拐
7A. Right.
右拐 6A
Right. 6A.
4A
4A.
3A
3A.
左 左 右 右
Left, left. Right, right.
左 左
Left, left.
好了 我能做到
Okay. I can do this.
恭喜你 罗斯
Congratulations, Rose.
你到了
You're here.
你成功了
You did it.
真相就是你的奖励
Your reward is the truth.
有没有看到小阿蕾莎多乖啊？
Did you see that Alessa was a good little girl?
尽管没有人这样认为
Even though nobody looked at her that way.
- 烧死这巫女！烧死她！- 她们的父母说她很坏
- Burn the witch! Burn the witch! - Their parents told them she was bad.
不像别人 她没有父亲
She didn't have a father like they did.
阿蕾莎一个人好孤单
Alessa was alone in the world.
你知道当小女孩一个人 会出什么事
You know what can happen to little girls when they're left alone.
（柯林）
没事 是我
It's okay, it's me, come on.
连她的妈妈也没有办法
Even her mother couldn't help.
尽管她深爱自己的孩子
Even though she loved her baby.
家里人都不爱阿蕾莎
But the rest of the family didn't love Alessa.
同那些人一样 令她感到害怕
They were just like the others and made her scared.
连小孩都知道
We know. Even the children know it.
你女儿
Your daughter…
为什么就不说出父亲的名字
Why you won't just name the father…
你给大家带来了罪恶
You've brought sin amongst us.
我们要集合众信徒进行审判
The faithful must gather in judgment…
好清洗这不洁之事
… for we are called to purify this filth.
妈咪 她说什么？
What does she mean, Mommy?
你太软弱 亲爱的妹妹 总是这样
You're weak, my dear sister. You always were.
相信我们 达利亚 相信大家的能力
Trust us, Dahlia. Have faith in our virtue.
我们会恢复清白
We will restore innocence.
建镇至今 集会过很多次
They had met many times since the town was built…
为了所谓的恢复清白和纯洁
… to restore innocence and purity.
还有个专门地方做法
They had a special place for that.
记不记得那个饭店？
Do you remember the hotel?
我带你去过所有的地方
I led you to all these places…
你都很好地跟随了我的线索
… and you were very good at following my clues.
你可以走了 达利亚
You may leave, Dahlia.
我们要斗的不是罪人 而是罪恶本身
We fight the sin, not the sinner.
妈咪！妈咪！
Mommy! Mommy!
妈咪！
Mommy!
罗斯 你能体会这种感受吧？
You know how that feels, don't you, Rose?
失去自己的女儿
To lose your little girl?
我做了什么？
What have I done?
- 天啊 - 不必为恶魔哭泣
- Oh, God. - Weep not for the demon.
不！
No!
又一次 我们面对生死存亡的战斗
Once again we are locked in mortal battle.
他们以为自己知道如何驱魔
They thought they knew how to cast out evil.
- 赞颂上帝赐我们清明 - 阿门
- Praise God for our clarity. - Amen.
赞颂清白之人所做的牺牲
Praise the innocent for their sacrifice.
不过要和恶魔战斗 可得小心
But you should be careful how you fight evil.
- 还我们以洁净 - 洁净
- They give us back our purity. - Purity.
- 还有团结 - 团结
- And our unity. - Unity.
你手里的武器 可能会反过来要你的命
Your weapons can turn back on you.
不
No.
现在你明白 为何达利亚会心碎
Now you know why Dahlia is broken.
她试着找人帮忙
She tried to get help…
可惜太迟了
… but she went too late.
架住她 快架住她！
Get her up, boys. Get her up now!
镇上也有好人
There were good people in the town…
跟你一样的好人 罗斯
… people like you, Rose.
是他们施以援手
People who like to help.
阿蕾莎好孤单 又痛苦又害怕
Alessa was so lonely and hurt and scared.
他们不该这样伤害她
They should have known better than to hurt her so badly.
当你被病痛和恐惧折磨太久
When you're hurt and scared for so long…
它们便会统统化作仇恨
… your fear and pain turn to hate…
而这种仇恨 开始改变周围的世界
… and the hate starts to change the world.
阿蕾莎的仇恨与日俱增 在她体内燃烧
Alessa's hate grew and grew, burning inside her.
恨意是那么强
Her hate got so strong…
就连仅仅是好奇的人都不放过
… she even hurt someone who was only curious.
这个时候我出现了
That's when I came.
我告诉她报复的时候到了
I told her it was their turn.
我保证他们都会落入她的噩梦中
I promised they would all fall into her darkest dream.
现在 罗斯 我们得谈谈
Now, Rose, we must talk.
别怕
Don't be afraid.
她不会伤害你
She won't hurt you.
她需要你的帮助
She needs your help.
她是谁？
Who is she?
- 阿蕾莎 - 那你是谁？
- She is Alessa. - Then who are you?
我有很多名字
I have many names.
现在 我是阿蕾莎的黑暗面
Right now, I'm the dark part of Alessa.
我孩子在哪？
Where's my child?
她不是你孩子
She's not your child.
是她的
She's hers.
她用仅存的善良 幻化出那个小女孩
The little girl is what's left of her goodness.
我们把她安全地藏好
We hid her in safety…
放到这炼狱以外的世界里
… in the world outside this hell.
托卢卡郡立孤儿院
Toluca County Orphanage
现在 她一生的噩梦该结束了
Now the dream of this life must end…
而梦里的人 也该做个了断了
… and so, too, must the dreamers within it.
30多年了
For over 30 years…
他们一直欺骗自己的灵魂
… they've lied to their own souls.
30年来始终否认自己的命运
For 30 years they've denied their own fate.
末日即将来临
But now is the end of days…
我收获的时候到了
… and I am the reaper.
你要什么？
What do you want?
我们要的只是满足
All we ask for is satisfaction.
满足？
Satisfaction?
复仇
Revenge.
为什么选我？
Why me?
你自己做的选择
You chose.
你选择了莎伦
You chose Sharon.
克里斯贝拉会找到莎伦
Christabella will find Sharon.
她会计划「清洁」她
She plans to purify her.
哦 天哪
Oh, God, no.
他们盲目的信念将我拦在教堂外
Their blind conviction repels me from their church.
只要他们不认命 我就进不去
I cannot enter while they deny their fate…
但你可以
… but you can.
- 告诉我该怎么做 - 说出真相
- Just tell me what I need to do. - Tell them the truth.
孩子是我的！
The child is mine!
我的！
Mine!
她是我的！
She's mine.
我的！
She's mine!
在目明之人面前 真相无比清晰
The truth is clear to those who see.
一如我当初看出你怀了孽种
Just as I could see you had this child.
我们走
Let's go.
下车 转过身去
Out of the car. Turn around.
一个善意的警告
Just a friendly warning…
我会带着明事理的人回来的
… I'll be back with people who know what they're doing.
在这之前 我想跟你谈谈伯纳特警官
Before you do that, Chris, I wanna tell you about Officer Bennett.
几年前 一个疯子拐了个男孩
Few years back, some wacko, he abducted a kid…
把他扔到寂静岭 一个矿井通风口里
… threw him down a mine vent up there in Silent Hill.
西比尔·伯纳特找到那个男孩
Cybil Bennett, she found that boy.
整整三天 她都抱着他
She spent three days holding onto him…
维持他的生命 直至获救
… keeping him alive until they were rescued.
我们自有分寸
We know what we're doing.
我也得尽我全力
I need to do everything I can.
我们走
Let's go.
求求你 克里斯贝拉 放她条生路
Please. Christabella, let her live.
你的软弱令这些灵魂受到审判
Your weakness led these souls to judgment.
- 这回你活该目睹这一切发生 - 她是无辜的
- This time you will bear witness. - She is innocent.
看看她 你女儿的孽种
Look at her. She's the whelp of your daughter.
恶魔！
The demon!
恶魔利用她的孩子孕育罪恶！
The demon fathered this disgusting abomination from her child!
不 她是我的！
No, she's mine!
莎伦 莎伦 看着我
Sharon. Sharon, look at me.
看着我 别害怕
Look at me. Don't be afraid.
没事 你妈妈马上就来
It's okay, it's okay. Your mama's coming.
又一次 我们为了恢复清白 聚到一起
Once again we are called upon to restore innocence.
烧死这巫女 征服邪恶
We burn this witch. We vanquish evil.
不 你们不能这样
No. You can't. You can't.
- 不 别任她瞎说！- 烧死这孽种！
- Don't let her say this! No! - We burn the child!
战胜恶魔！
We fight the demon!
她只是个孩子啊！
She's just a child!
你们他妈的是怎么回事？
What the fuck is wrong with you people?
让她走！
Let her go!
不许碰她！
Leave her alone!
助纣为虐者
Those who aid the demon…
也要接受地狱之火的净化！
… they must be cleansed by the fire from whence they came!
疯了 你们都疯了
That's crazy. You're crazy.
不！
No!
你们为什么都相信她？
Why are you listening to this?
为什么？
Why?
烧死巫女！烧死她！
Burn the witch! Burn her!
Burn the witch! Burn her! Burn the witch!
莎伦
Sharon.
邪恶的巫女！
Evil witch!
受罪吧
Suffer.
烧死巫女！烧死她！
Burn the witch! Burn her!
噢 天啊
Oh, my God.
烧死巫女！烧死她！
Burn the witch! Burn her! Burn the witch! Burn her!
烧死她！
Burn her!
你们自作孽 必下地狱
You're in your own hell.
妈妈啊 救救我
Mama, be with me.
天启就此开始
Here is where the apocalypse began.
对世界的毁灭已经结束
This is where we stopped the annihilation of the world.
在地上 我们划出界限
We drew a line in the sand and said:
说：「恶魔 你无法越过！」
"Demon, you will not cross!"
但是恶魔叛逆而阴险
But the demon is wicked, full of treachery.
再一次带上无辜的面具来诱惑我们
Yet again he comes to tempt us in the guise of an innocent.
要铲除恶魔
To rid the world of this demon…
就要烧死这孩子！
… we must burn this child!
你不会得逞的
That's not gonna happen!
妈咪！
Mommy!
没事了 宝贝
It's okay, baby. Everything's gonna be okay.
天哪
Oh, my God.
你们都做了些什么？
What have you people done?
- 你回来了 - 是的
- You have returned. - Yes, I have.
巫女回来了
The witch has returned.
别信她的鬼话
Do not believe her lies.
我从外面的世界来
I come from a world outside this place.
从一个生机勃勃的世界来！
I come from a world full of life!
为什么不告诉他们真相？
Why don't you tell them the truth?
那个连你自己都否认的真相
Tell them the truth that you deny, even to yourself.
根本没有天启！
There was no apocalypse!
你们活在自己制造的炼狱里
You burned in the fire that you started…
无可救赎 因为你们都被诅咒了！
… and nothing can save you because you're already damned!
- 妈咪！- 把她抓起来
- Mommy! - Take her.
烧！把她当巫女烧死！
Burn her! Burn her as a witch!
烧死她！
Burn her! Burn her!
巫女！
Demon witch!
- 烧死我？- 巫女
- Burn me? - Demon witch.
这就是你的对策？
That's your answer?
烧死你所惧怕的
Burn anything you're afraid of.
烧光不受你控制的
Burn anything you can't control.
这女人 利用你们的恐惧来控制你们
This woman uses your fear to control you.
她指使你们烧阿蕾莎·格雷斯彼
She led you to burn Alessa Gillespie.
她指使你们烧一个无辜的孩子
She led you to burn an innocent child.
但你们无法否认你们的罪行
But you will not deny your guilt…
无法否认她的痛苦！
… and you cannot deny her pain!
那个孩子是罪恶的化身
That child was sin incarnate.
不 你才犯下罪过
No, it's you who have sinned.
过去你丑化一颗无辜的心灵
You darkened the heart of an innocent…
现在又惧怕阿蕾莎的复仇
… and now you cower in the face of Alessa's revenge.
邪说
Sinner. Heresy.
烧死她！烧死她！
Burn her! Burn her!
你们的信仰将带来灭顶之灾！
Your faith brings death!
你们在地狱门口 孤立无助
You are alone in this limbo…
因为上帝不在那儿
… and God is not here.
妈咪！
Mommy!
她是亵渎者！
She was a blasphemer!
亵渎者！
Blasphemer!
你做了什么？
What have you done?
你把黑暗带了进来
You've brought the darkness in with you.
知道你做了什么吗？
Do you know what you've done?
为了莎伦
For Sharon.
妈咪
Mommy.
Mommy. Mommy.
妈咪！
Mommy!
主啊 请助我保持纯净！
Oh, Lord, give me the strength to stay pure!
不！
No! No!
阿蕾莎 你都做了些什么？
Alessa, what have you become?
妈咪！
Mommy!
莎伦！宝贝 妈妈来了
Sharon! Sharon, honey, it's me. It's Mommy.
下来了 我们下来了
Down. We're getting down.
闭上眼 乖 闭上眼
Shut your eyes. Shut your eyes, baby.
闭上眼 快闭上
Shut your eyes. Shut your eyes.
只是个噩梦 噩梦
It's just a bad dream. It's just a bad dream.
为什么她不要我的命？
Why did she not take me with the others?
因为你是他母亲
Because you're her mother.
在孩子眼里 母亲就是上帝
Mother is God in the eyes of a child.
我爱你
I love you.
- 你好 我是克里斯 - 我是罗斯
- Hi, this is Chris. - And this is Rose.
我是莎伦·达·西尔瓦
And I'm Sharon Da Silva.
请留言！
Please leave a message!
克里斯托弗 是我
Christopher, it's me.
我和莎伦在一起
I'm with Sharon.
喂？喂？罗斯？
Hello? Hello? Rose?
罗斯？
Rose?
嗯 我们这就回家
Yeah. We're coming home.